<idea-plugin>

    <id>ru.masterdata.idea.plugin.commerce.integration</id>
    <name>SAP Commerce (hybris)</name>
    <version>2019.1.1</version>

    <!-- http://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/build_number_ranges.html -->
    <idea-version since-build="191"/>

    <vendor email="valentin.kulesh@masterdata.ru" url="https://masterdata.ru">Valentin Kulesh</vendor>

    <!-- language=HTML -->
    <description>
        <![CDATA[
        <p>This is an unofficial community-maintained plugin for SAP Commerce (f.k.a. hybris) integration with
            IntelliJ IDEA.</p>

        <b>Features:</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Import of hybris extensions as IntelliJ IDEA modules with automatic dependency resolution and classpath
                optimized for fast compilation and correct tests execution.
            </li>
            <li>Automatic configuration of Spring, Web, Ant, Database-related features of IntelliJ IDEA.</li>
            <li>Import your custom Eclipse, Maven and Gradle extensions together with hybris platform.</li>
            <li>Custom editor for FlexibleSearch queries capable to execute queries on remote hybris instances right
                from the IDE with a single click.
            </li>
            <li>Custom editor for ImpEx files with pretty formatting, "Find Usages", "Go To Declaration", validation and
                import of ImpExes into remote hybris instances right from the IDE with a single click.
            </li>
            <li>Custom editor for items.xml with validation, best-practices analysis, quick-fix autosuggestion and easy
                navigation.
            </li>
            <li>Custom editor for beans.xml with refactorings actions.</li>
            <li>Visualization of business process graph (use context menu of the file "Diagrams/Show Diagram", only
                Ultimate IDEA).
            </li>
            <li>Enhanced project view tree.</li>
            <li>JRebel and DCEVM support.</li>
            <li>Execution of Flexible Search queries, Groovy scripts, ImpExes though IDE using hAC Integration tool.
            </li>
            <li>Execution of queries on remote Solr instances.</li>
            <li>And much more</li>
        </ul>

        <p>This plugin is a derivative from plugin originally started by Alexander Bartash and released under GPL 3.0
            license.</p>
        <p>If you prefer using the now closed source premium featured version of the plugin, visit
            https://plugins.jetbrains.com/plugin/7525-hybris-integration</p>
        ]]>
    </description>

    <!-- language=HTML -->
    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
        <h2>Changes in 2019.1.1</h2>
        <ul>
            <li>Initial version for Masterdata Soup</li>
        </ul>
        ]]>
    </change-notes>
</idea-plugin>
