<idea-plugin>

    <id>com.intellij.idea.plugin.sap.commerce</id>
    <name>SAP Commerce Developers Toolset</name>
    <!-- It is mandatory to have 3 values for version due validation of the project, which is done by DefaultCommonIdeaService -->
    <version>2022.3.1</version>

    <!-- http://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/build_number_ranges.html -->
    <idea-version since-build="223.7571.58" until-build="223.*"/>

    <vendor email="hybrisideaplugin@epam.com"
            url="https://github.com/epam/sap-commerce-intellij-idea-plugin">
        EPAM Systems
    </vendor>

    <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>This plugin is a plugin for SAP Commerce Cloud integration.</p>

          <b>If you have any questions you can send an email to:</b>
          <ul>
              <li><a href="mailto:hybrisideaplugin@epam.com">EPAM Systems</a></li>
          </ul>

          <b>Features:</b>
          <ul>
              <li>Import of Hybris extensions to Intellij IDEA with automatic dependency resolution and classpath configuration optimized for fast compilation.</li>
              <li>Automatic configuration of Spring, Web, Ant, Database Connector Intellij IDEA plugins.</li>
              <li>Import your custom Eclipse, Maven and Gradle extensions together with Hybris platform.</li>
              <li>Custom editor for flexible Search queries with an ability to execute them on a remote Hybris instance right from your IDE by a single click of a button.</li>
              <li>Custom editor for impex files with automatic formatting, find usages and go to declaration actions, validation and import of impexes into a remote Hybris instance right from your IDE by a single click of a button.</li>
              <li>Custom editor for items.xml with validation, best-practices analyses, quick-fix autosuggestion and easy navigation.</li>
              <li>Custom editor for beans.xml with custom automated Intellij refactorings actions.</li>
              <li>Visualization of business process graph (use context menu of the file "Diagrams/Show Diagram", only Ultimate IDEA).</li>
              <li>Enhanced project view tree.</li>
              <li>Execution of Flexible Search queries, Groovy scripts, Impexes though IDE using HAC Integration tool.</li>
              <li>Execution of queries on remote Solr instances.</li>
              <li>And much more</li>
          </ul>

          <b>Contribution guidelines:</b>
          <ul>
              <li>Please read <a href="https://developercertificate.org/">Contributor License Agreement</a></li>
              <li>Available tasks are in our board: <a href="https://github.com/epam/sap-commerce-intellij-idea-plugin/projects/1">Project board</a></li>
              <li><a href="https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/setting_up_environment.html">How to Configure Project Environment For Plugin Developers</a></li>
              <li>We are working with <a href="https://help.github.com/articles/about-pull-requests/">Pull Requests</a>. You need to fork this repository, implement a feature in a separate branch, then send us a pull request.</li>
              <li>Be sure to include into your pull request and all commit messages the following line: "Signed-off-by: Your Real Name your.email@email.com" otherwise it can not be accepted. Use your real name.</li>
              <li>For additional questions you can send an <a href="mailto:hybrisideaplugin@epam.com">email</a></li>
          </ul>

          <b>Contributors and Developers</b>
          <p>This project exists thanks to all the people who contribute.</p>

          <ul>
              <li>Alexander Bartash</li>
              <li>Vlad Bozhenok</li>
              <li>Martin Zdarsky-Jones</li>
              <li>Alexander Nosov</li>
              <li>Eugene Kudelevsky</li>
              <li>Cristian Caprar</li>
              <li>Daniel Carter</li>
              <li>Oleksandr Mishchuk</li>
              <li>Michael Golubev</li>
              <li>Nicko Cadell</li>
              <li>Dan Wanigasekera</li>
              <li>Markus Priegl</li>
              <li>Sergei Aksenenko</li>
              <li>Roger Ye</li>
              <li>Hector Longarte</li>
              <li>Fabian Necci</li>
              <li>Markus Perndorfer</li>
              <li>FAIR Consulting Group</li>
              <li>Mykyta Kostiuk</li>
              <li>Dmytro Lytvynenko</li>
              <li>Oleksandr Shkurat</li>
              <li>Maxim Bilohay</li>
              <li>Eugene Koryakin</li>
              <li>Yevhenii Koshevyi</li>
              <li>Mykhailo Lytvyn</li>
              <li>Viktors Jengovatovs</li>
              <li>Oleksandr Dihtiar</li>
              <li>Rustam Burmenskyi</li>
              <li>Vladyslav Yanytskyi</li>
          </ul>
      ]]>
    </description>

    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
            <ul>
                <li> Introduced the Bean System Management - the powerful tool to observe SAP Commerce bean system </li>
                <li> Added possibility to preview preformatted Flexible Search Queries and copy them to Clipboard </li>
                <li> Added customized Structure View for beans.xml files </li>
                <li> Added new beans.xml inspection rules </li>
                <li> Added navigation to items.xml Type attributes from generated classes </li>
                <li> Added navigation to beans.xml Enum values declaration from generated classes </li>
                <li> Added navigation to beans.xml Bean property declaration from generated classes </li>
                <li> Added extra visibility filters for Type System view </li>
                <li> Added <strong>dynamic</strong> prefix getters/setters in the Java classes </li>
                <li> Added <strong>dynamic</strong> flag for attribute suggestions in the impex files </li>
                <li> Inspection for beans.xml rely on whole Bean System, not only current file </li>
                <li> Decreased usage of the Deprecated API </li>
                <li> Fixed: Business Process Diagram action is not visible </li>
                <li> Fixed: Impex config processor inspection rule </li>
                <li> Fixed: Default values for Type System modifiers </li>
            </ul>

            <strong>Ultimate only</strong>
            <ul>
                <li> Introduced new items.xml Annotator for Attribute Handler </li>
            </ul>
          ]]>
    </change-notes>

</idea-plugin>
