<idea-plugin>

    <id>ccom.intellij.idea.plugin.commerce.integration</id>
    <name>Integration for SAP Commerce</name>
    <version>2019.2</version>

    <!-- http://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/build_number_ranges.html -->
    <idea-version since-build="191"/>

    <vendor email="commerceplugin@janhouse.lv"
            url="https://github.com/Janhouse/sap-commerce-integration-intellij-idea-plugin">
        Janis Jansons
    </vendor>

    <description>
        <![CDATA[
          <p>This is an unofficial community maintained plugin for SAP Commerce (previously Hybris) integration within IntelliJ IDEA.</p>

          <p>This plugin was forked by developers sometime in 2017 and two versions were maintained by original developers - LGPL 3.0 licensed
          one for public contributions and private one that was released on JetBrains plugin repository that possibly contained
          both private changes and public ones from LGPL 3.0 version. By doing so they potentially broke the terms of LGPL 3.0 license.</p>
          <p>If you are using older IntelliJ IDEA version with older plugin version they should provide source code with all
          of the features if you request it.</p>

          <p>Here is a list of features in the free, open source version of the plugin.</p>

          <b>Working features:</b>
          <ul>
              <li>✅ Import of SAP Commerce extensions to Intellij IDEA with automatic dependency resolution and classpath configuration optimized for fast compilation</li>
              <li>✅ Automatic configuration of Spring, Web, Ant, Database Connector Intellij IDEA plugins</li>
              <li>✅ Import your custom Eclise, Maven and Gradle extensions together with SAP Commerce platform</li>
              <li>✅ Custom editor for impex files with automatic formatting, find usages and go to declaration actions, validation and import of impexes into a remote SAP Commerce instance right from your IDE by single click of a button</li>
              <li>✅ Custom editor for items.xml with validation, best-practices analyses, quick-fix autosuggestion and easy navigation</li>
              <li>✅ Custom editor for beans.xml with custom automated Intellij refactorings actions</li>
              <li>✅ Visualization of business process graph (use context menu of the file "Diagrams/Show Diagram", only Ultimate IDEA)</li>
              <li>✅ Enhanced project view tree</li>
              <li>✅ JRebel and DCEVM support</li>
              <li>✅ Execution of Groovy scripts, Impexes through IDE using HAC Integration tool</li>
              <li>And some more</li>
          </ul>

          <b>Missing from LGPL version:</b>
          <ul>
              <li>🚫 JunitTest runner configuration (but tests can still be run)</li>
              <li>🚫 Execution of Flexible Search queries through IDE using HAC Integration tool</li>
              <li>🚫 Execution of queries on remote Solr instances</li>
              <li>🚫 Custom editor for flexible Search queries with an ability to execute them on a remote SAP Commerce instance right from your IDE by single click of a button</li>
          </ul>

          <p>This plugin is a derivative from plugin originally started by Alexander Bartash and released under GPL 3.0 license.</p>
          <p>If you prefer using the now closed source premium featured version of the plugin, visit https://plugins.jetbrains.com/plugin/7525-hybris-integration</p>

      ]]>
    </description>

    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
            <h2>Changes in 2019.2</h2>
            <ul>
                <li>Updated feature description and readme</li>
            </ul>
        ]]>
    </change-notes>
</idea-plugin>
